

# Karlo Orlandini

+44 77 091 <u>095 15</u>

orlandinikarlo@gmail.com

Birmingham, B37 6NS United

Kingdom

https://karlox01.github.io/My-CV-Karlo/ **WWW:** https://www.linkedin.com/in/karlo-orlandini-a86b25218/

#### **SKILLS**

- · Time Management
- Fourth Shift
- Accounting Systems and Software
- Order book Management
- Internal Audits
- Quality Audits
- Month-End Reports
- Microsoft Office
- Data Analysis
- Programming / Software Development

Croatian: Native language

#### **LANGUAGES**

English: C2
Proficient
Italian: A2
Elementary
Polish: A1

Beginner

### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am a dedicated friendly and meticulous person, With excellent experience in industry. Maintains professional appearance and demeanor and expertly completes assigned tasks with focus on quality. Dependable and quick-learning team player with effective communication and organization skills.

#### **WORK HISTORY**

October 2021 - Current

Customer Service / Accounting Clerk, HydraForce LTD, Birmingham

Serve as the main point of contact in all matters related to client concerns and needs Build and strengthen client relationships to achieve long-term partnerships Maintain accurate client records, keeping track of any contract updates and renewals Work with sales and other internal teams to develop strategic marketing plans and ensure KPIs are being met Handle inquiries and requests from customers and address their needs

Stay on top of accounts, making sure they receive services that are within their budget and meet their needs

Meet regularly with other team members to discuss progress and find new ways to improve business

June 2019 - July 2021

Shift Leader Manager, Dunlop Aircraft Tyres, Birmingham

Supervision of the shift to deliver the production targets in dynamic piece work environment.

Support the team in the implementation of new initiatives ie 5s, housekeeping etc. Effectively communicate the business expectations to the staff on a daily basis through effective start of shift meeting.

Maintain the departmental KPI information boards with up to date performance data. Provide information of issues to the daily production meetings to ensure that all

Problem solving on a daily basis to mitigate loss of product.

opportunities for improvement are captured and implemented.

Provide an audit report for the product, components and tools supplied to the department.

Create the weekly departmental plan to ensure schedule adherence.

Implementation of the 5s programme.

Involved in regular PM schedules.

Support the staff training and development of trainees. Absence monitoring and conduct return to work interviews.

July 2015 - June 2019

Internal Auditor /Trainer, Dunlop Aircraft Tyres, Birmingham

I have quickly rose through ranks at DATL, And have made a trainer, Shortly also a fully certified ISO Internal Auditor.

Some of the responsibilities include but are not limited to: Liaise with managers to determine training needs and schedule training sessions.

Design effective training programs.

Conduct individual training sessions etc.

Keep a detailed report on the Trainee's performance.

Gathering and analyzing data.

July 2014 - June 2015

Administrator, UKMail, Birmingham

Maintain a filing system for data on customers and external partners.

Word processing and data entry

Tracking of the deliveries, And lost ma

### **EDUCATION**

Expected in 2024

Associate Degree In IT, Information Technology
University Of North Scotland / Code Institute , Scotland, United Kingdom

2012

College Undergrad Degree., Maritime Studies Pomorska Skola Split, Split, Croatia

## DIVING, WATERSPORTS, SWIMMING.

Born and raised in a coastal city of Split, It is not all that strange i have always had a passion for the sea. From the earliest age , My favorite hobbies were tied to it, Including Kayaking, Diving, Fishing.

It was also the reason i enrolled into maritime college.